aboutbritain.com 2012-12-23

# AboutBritain.com - Privacy

### Privacy Statement

Excelsior Information Systems Limited, owners of the AboutBritain.com web site, respect your privacy and confidentiality as a user of the site. We have provided this statement of our Privacy Policy as a demonstration of our commitment to your privacy online. 

Our servers note non-personally identifying details such as, but not limited to, the operating system you use, the type of browser you use, and your IP address. We use this information (usually in aggregate) to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and in aggregate to gather broad demographic and system information to allow us to design our site to appear correctly on the various systems our viewers use. 

Cookies are used by AboutBritain.com and companies who serve advertising on our site to improve your web browsing experience. When you are first served an ad, we may assign a unique random number to your computer browser - commonly known as a "cookie." We do this to understand the way a user responds to the ads we deliver. For example, this number lets us keep track of how many times you have seen a particular ad. Therefore, the cookie can help make sure you do not see the same ad over and over - thus enhancing your online web viewing experience.

We also use cookies to track the effectiveness of our own online advertising, by noting which of our adverts (if any) you responded to. This allows us to optimise our advertising; our customers therefore benefit from our use of cookies as they help to minimise our advertising costs and to keep our prices low. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can delete cookies from your machine, and change the settings on your browser to prevent the acceptance of cookies if you desire. You will find more information about cookies, including how to control, refuse, or delete them on [this site](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

We have contracted with Google for the purpose of reporting web traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our site. Where authorised by us, Google may compile anonymous statistics on our Web site visitors. This will be anonymous data, showing how often specific pages have been viewed, or links clicked. For more information on Google's privacy policy, please see [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html). 

Our online hotel reservation facilities are provided under an agreement with Superbreak.com and ActiveHotels.com. In the case of hotel bookings made on this site, Superbreak.com's or ActiveHotel.com's privacy policy would also apply, depending on which partner the booking was made through. 

Advertising Cookies: This site has contracted with Travel Ad Network and its third party ad-serving technology provider Atlas, a Microsoft Corporation Subsidiary, to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', advertisement impressions, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, Travel Ad Network may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by Travel Ad Network, please see Travel Ad Network's privacy policy at <http://www.traveladnetwork.com/content/view/56/79/>. 

Cookies are important devices for both serving more relevant ads to users and measuring advertising effectiveness. You may opt out of accepting cookies at any time by clicking these links: To opt out of TravelAdvertising.com, go to <http://www.traveladnetwork.com/content/view/56/79/>. To opt out of Atlas (Microsoft Advertising), go to <http://www.atlassolutions.com/optout.aspx>. 

AboutBritain.com contains many links to external sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those sites, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of third-party sites. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact AboutBritain.com

 [Copyright](http://www.aboutbritain.com/TermsAndCopyright.htm) © 1999-2012 Excelsior Information Systems Ltd. All rights reserved.
